yaleappliance.com 2019-03-30

# Yale Appliance + Lighting | Boston Kitchen Appliances Showroom

Welcome to the Yale Appliance, Inc. (“Yale”) website www.yaleappliance.com. Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.yaleappliance.com and www.blog.yaleappliance.com and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Yale Appliance, Inc. include www.yaleappliance.com, www.blog.yaleappliance.com and Yale. The Yale website is a retail sales and service site. By using the Yale website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**

In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Yale may collect personally identifiable information, such as your: 

  * First and Last Name 
  * Mailing Address
  * E-mail Address
  * Phone Number
  * IP addresses
  * Site access dates and times

If you purchase Yale’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. **We will not share your information** with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. 

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. 

**Use of your Personal Information**

Yale collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. 

Yale may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Yale and its affiliates. 

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: 

  * See what data we have about you, if any. 
  * Change/correct any data we have about you. 
  * Have us delete any data we have about you. 
  * Have us delete any data we have about you. 
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

**Yale does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.**

Yale may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Yale, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

Yale may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Yale or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Yale; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Yale, or the public. 

**Tracking User Behavior**

Yale may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Yale, in order to determine what Yale services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Yale to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

**Automatically Collected Information**

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Yale. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Yale website. 

**Use of Cookies**

The Yale website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Yale pages, or register with Yale site or services, a cookie helps Yale to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Yale website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Yale features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Yale services or websites you visit. 

**Links**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**Security of your Personal Information**

Yale secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Yale uses the following methods for this purpose: 

  * SSL Protocol 

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. 

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed. 

**E-mail Communications**

From time to time, Yale may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. 

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from W, you may opt out of such communications by send an unsubscribe email to webmaster@yaleappliance.com 

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**External Data Storage Sites**

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted. 

**Consent**

By using our site, you consent to all terms contained herein. 

**Changes to this Statement**

Yale reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy. 

**Contact Information**

Yale welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Yale has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Yale at: 

Yale Appliance, Inc.   
37 Shuman Avenue  
Stoughton, Massachusetts 02072 

Email Address: [webmaster@yaleappliance.com](mailto:webmaster@yaleappliance.com)

Telephone number: [617-979-6099](tel:6179796099)

Effective as of 02/12/2019
